[
     {
          "exam_name": "biology",
          "questions": [
               {
                    "question": "The hormone Erythropoietin is produced in______",
                    "answer_a": "Liver",
                    "answer_b": "Spleen",
                    "answer_c": "Kidney",
                    "answer_d": "Thyroid gland",
                    "answer_right": "Kidney"
               },
               {
                    "question": "For some integer n, the odd integer is represented in the form of:",
                    "answer_a": "n",
                    "answer_b": "n + 1",
                    "answer_c": "2n + 1",
                    "answer_d": "2n",
                    "answer_right": "2n + 1"
               },
               {
                    "question": "Which of the following is not irrational?",
                    "answer_a": "(3 + √7)",
                    "answer_b": "(3 – √7)",
                    "answer_c": "(3 + √7) (3 – √7)",
                    "answer_d": "3√7",
                    "answer_right": "(3 + √7) (3 – √7)"
               },
               {
                    "question": "The addition of a rational number and an irrational number is equal to:",
                    "answer_a": "rational number",
                    "answer_b": "Irrational numbe",
                    "answer_c": "Both",
                    "answer_d": "None of the above",
                    "answer_right": "Irrational numbe"
               },
               {
                    "question": "If set A = {1, 2, 3, 4, 5,…} is given, then it represents:",
                    "answer_a": "Whole numbers",
                    "answer_b": "Rational Numbers",
                    "answer_c": "Natural numbers",
                    "answer_d": " Complex numbers",
                    "answer_right": "Natural numbers"
               },
               {
                    "question": "If p and q are integers and is represented in the form of p/q, then it is a:",
                    "answer_a": "Whole number",
                    "answer_b": "Rational number",
                    "answer_c": "Natural number",
                    "answer_d": "Even number",
                    "answer_right": "Rational number"
               },
               {
                    "question": "The largest number that divides 70 and 125, which leaves the remainders 5 and 8, is:",
                    "answer_a": "65",
                    "answer_b": "15",
                    "answer_c": "13",
                    "answer_d": "25",
                    "answer_right": "13"
               },
               {
                    "question": "The decimal expansion of the rational number 23/(22 . 5) will terminate after",
                    "answer_a": "one decimal place",
                    "answer_b": "two decimal places",
                    "answer_c": "three decimal places",
                    "answer_d": "more than 3 decimal places",
                    "answer_right": "two decimal places"
               },
               {
                    "question": " Euclid’s division lemma states that for two positive integers a and b, there exist unique integers q and r such that a = bq + r, where r must satisfy",
                    "answer_a": "1 < r < b ",
                    "answer_b": "0 < r ≤ b",
                    "answer_c": "0 ≤ r < b ",
                    "answer_d": "0 < r < b",
                    "answer_right": "0 ≤ r < b "
               },
               {
                    "question": "The prime factorisation of 96 is",
                    "answer_a": "2^5 × 3",
                    "answer_b": "2^6",
                    "answer_c": "2^4 × 3",
                    "answer_d": "2^4 × 32",
                    "answer_right": "2^5 × 3"
               }
          ]
     },
     { "exam_name": "networking",
          "questions": [
            {
              "question": "Which Rapid Spanning Tree Protocol port state is a combination of standard 802.1D STP's disabled, blocking and listening states?",
              "answer_a": "Blocking",
              "answer_b": "Discarding",
              "answer_c": "Learning",
              "answer_d": "Forwarding",
              "answer_right": "Discarding"
            },
            {
              "question": "Host A receives a frame and discards it after determining it is corrupt. Which OSI layer checks frames for errors?",
              "answer_a": "Physical",
              "answer_b": "Data-link",
              "answer_c": "Application",
              "answer_d": "Network",
              "answer_right": "Data-link"
            },
            {
              "question": "No matter how it's configured, a single switch port is considered what?",
              "answer_a": "A separate unicast domain",
              "answer_b": "A separate broadcast domain",
              "answer_c": "A separate multicast domain",
              "answer_d": "A separate collision domain",
              "answer_right": "A separate collision domain"
            },
            {
              "question": "Identify which of the services below uses both TCP and UDP ports.",
              "answer_a": "FTP",
              "answer_b": "TFTP",
              "answer_c": "DNS",
              "answer_d": "Telnet",
              "answer_right": "DNS"
            },
        {
              "question": "A router with a BGP autonomous system number of 65001 is peered with another router with the same BGP AS. Which of the following is true?",
              "answer_a": "The ebgp multihop command must be configured to reach an established state.",
              "answer_b": "The routers are considered iBGP neighbors.",
              "answer_c": "A BGP establishment error will occur because of the AS conflict.",
              "answer_d": "The routers are considered eBGP neighbors.",
              "answer_right": "The routers are considered iBGP neighbors."
            },
        {
              "question": "No matter how it's configured, a single switch port is considered what?",
              "answer_a": "A separate unicast domain",
              "answer_b": "A separate broadcast domain",
              "answer_c": "A separate multicast domain",
              "answer_d": "A separate collision domain",
              "answer_right": "A separate collision domain"
            },
        {
              "question": "What is the default 802.1D short spanning tree port cost of a 10 Gbps Ethernet link?",
              "answer_a": "10",
              "answer_b": "4",
              "answer_c": "2",
              "answer_d": "2000",
              "answer_right": "2"
            },
        {
              "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to configure a switch port as a standard user port on VLAN 10 for data and VLAN 50 for VoIP?",
              "answer_a": "TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport mode trunk TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport access vlan 10 TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport voice vlan 50",
              "answer_b": "TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport mode access TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport access vlan 10 TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport voice vlan 50",
              "answer_c": "TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport mode access TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport access vlan 10 TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport voip vlan 50",
              "answer_d": "TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport mode access TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport access vlan 50 TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport voice vlan 10",
              "answer_right": "TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport mode access TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport access vlan 10 TechTarget-SW1(config-if)#switchport voice vlan 50"
            },
        {
              "question": "Your manager has requested you indicate which of the above ports will be Spanning Tree Protocol-designated ports.",
              "answer_a": "Switch V1, Port Fa0/0; Switch V3, Port Fa0/0; Switch V3, Port Fa0/24",
              "answer_b": "Switch V1, Port Fa0/24; Switch V0, Port Fa0/0; Switch V1, Port Fa0/24",
              "answer_c": "Switch V1, Port Fa0/24; Switch V1, Port Fa0/0; Switch V2, Port Fa0/24",
              "answer_d": "Switch V1, Port Fa0/24; Switch V2, Port Fa0/0; Switch V2, Port Fa0/24",
              "answer_right": "Switch V1, Port Fa0/24; Switch V2, Port Fa0/0; Switch V2, Port Fa0/24"
            },
        {
              "question": "Which of the following EXEC commands will reset LLDP traffic error counters?",
              "answer_a": "clear lldp",
              "answer_b": "clear lldp counters",
              "answer_c": "clear table lldp",
              "answer_d": "clear lldp table",
              "answer_right": "clear lldp counters"
            }
          ]
        }
        
        
]